Someone eventually
is gonna call me out for stealing content
ideas.
Not just any ideas, ideas
that have made me tens of thousands of
dollars.
I just want to get ahead of these
allegations and just come clean with
exactly what
I've done and why I've done it.
In front of me here is Iman Gadzhi.
Whether you're a believer in his courses
or his entrepreneurial skills, there's one
thing we can't deny.
His channel performs incredibly well.
I have it on good authority
that he has a rather large team of very
intelligent,
smart people,
that every single thing he does
is incredibly strategic.
And if we go onto his videos,
with a vidIQ plugin, we can see
that some videos
perform better than others. And down here,
there is an outlier, 7.9
times better than any of his other videos.
So for it to be an outlier on his channel,
I thought surely this can be an outlier
on my channel.